http://www.ski.com/privacy

Navigate traveling during COVID-19RSVP now for a Refundable Ski Vacation PackageToggle navigationMenuAustraliaCanadaUnited KingdomIrelandMexicoBrazilAccount1-800-908-5000 RSVP now for a Refundable Ski Vacation Package: 1-970-429-3099 | 7AM - 9PM MTExploreSki ResortsResort FinderBlogPlan your tripLodgingDealsGroupsRSVPCOVID-19Zoom with a Ski ExpertGuidedGuided tripsHeliCat skiingGet your free quote nowFree QuotePromotions‹›Ski.com Privacy Policy
Below you will find the Privacy Policy describing the types of information that Ski.com collects from and about you when you use the Ski.com website (www.Ski.com), Ski.com mobile application (“mobile app”) and services of Ski.com (collectively, the “Ski.com Service”). We value your trust, and make it a high priority to ensure the security and confidentiality of the personal information you provide to us. Please read this policy to learn about our privacy practices. By using the Ski.com Service, you are accepting the practices described herein.
What information we collect from you
In General. We receive and store any information you enter on our website or give us in any other way, such as signing up for one of our e-mail newsletters or other services. This includes information that can identify you ("personal information"), including your first and last name, telephone number, postal and email addresses, and billing information (such as credit or debit card number, cardholder name, expiration date, and billing address). We may also request additional information, such as your hotel room preferences, requests for special services or meal requests, and frequent flyer and car rental program information. You can choose not to provide this additional information to us, but in general certain personal or other information about you is required to register as a member and create a member profile; book travel; complete a traveler profile; participate in a survey, contest, promotion, or sweepstakes; ask us a question; or initiate other transactions on our site.
Travel Companion Information When you make a reservation for someone else through this website, we will request personal and other information and travel preferences about that individual. You should obtain the consent of other individuals prior to providing us with their personal information and travel preferences. For your convenience, we make certain information about your reservation available to you or other persons authorized by you to receive such information. For example, if you forget your flight number, you or another person authorized by you may retrieve that information from us after confirming your or their identity.
TSA Secure Flight Under the Transportation Security Administration (TSA) Secure Flight program, most air passengers are now required to provide their full name, date of birth, and gender (plus redress number, when applicable). Secure Flight is a federally mandated program administered by the TSA. The privacy notice of the TSA is provided on TSA's Web site at www.tsa.gov.
Information from Other Sources
We also may periodically obtain both personal and non-personal information about you from affiliated entities, business partners and other independent third-party sources and add it to our account information. Examples of information we may receive include: updated delivery and address information, purchase history, and demographic information. In addition, if you sign up for Ski.com using your social media account, link your Ski.com account to your social media account, or use certain other Ski.com social media features, we may access information about you via that social media provider in accordance with the provider's policies. The information may include your name, email address, profile picture, gender, list of friends, and other information that you authorize us to receive. Depending on the privacy settings of you and your friends, we may access information that you provide to a social media provider regarding your respective locations ("Location Data") to provide you with relevant content. Please note that your Location Data may also be shared with your friends on a social media provider in accordance with your privacy settings for that social media provider.
Automatic Information
We automatically collect some information about your computer or device, and your computer’s or device’s connection to the Internet when you visit this website or use the Ski.com Service. For example, we will collect your IP address, device information, operating system, Web browser software (such as Firefox, Safari, or Internet Explorer), and referring website. We also may collect information about your activities while using the Ski.com Service, such as trips viewed and bookings made. Our goals in collecting this automatic information include helping customize your user experience, diagnosing problems with our servers, administering our systems, and helping to prevent fraud or unauthorized use of our Ski.com Service. For more information, please see the “cookies and other technologies” section.
How we use your information
We use sensitive billing information (such as cardholder name, credit card number, and expiration date) for the purpose of completing the travel bookings you conduct on our site. We use other information about you for the following general purposes: to provide you with the products and services you request; to provide you with travel confirmation and updates; to manage your account, including processing bills and providing travel notifications; to communicate with you in general; to respond to your questions and comments; to measure interest in and improve our products, services, and website; to notify you about special offers and products or services that may be of interest to you; to otherwise customize your experience with this website; to reward you as part of any reward and recognition program you choose to join; to solicit information from you, including through surveys; to resolve disputes, collect fees, or troubleshoot problems; to prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities; to enforce our Terms of Use; and as otherwise described to you at the point of collection. We may also use Location Data, as discussed further in the “Using the Ski.com Mobile Apps” section.
**Email communications
We want to make it easy for you to take advantage of travel-related opportunities on our website. One way we do this is by sending you email messages that contain information about your apparent travel-related interests. For example, if you search for a flight to a ski destination on our website and have saved your itinerary or otherwise not yet booked your travel, we may send you an email message reminding you about your saved travel itinerary or about a special airfare to your destination. Similarly, if you receive an email from us about ski travel and demonstrate an interest in hotels by affirmatively clicking on a link about hotels at the resort in the email, you may receive an email about hotel offers or other destination information. We believe these email messages will provide you with useful information about travel-related special offers available through our site. Please note that you will have the opportunity to choose not to receive these email messages in any such email we send.
Please review "Your choices with respect to the collection and use of your information" below.
With whom we share your information
This website may share your information with the following entities:
Suppliers such as hotel, airline, car rental, cruise line, and activity providers, who fulfill your travel reservations. Throughout this site, all services provided by a third-party supplier are described as such. By making a reservation through this site, you are authorizing us to disclose to suppliers the information required to complete the booking and deliver the related travel. These suppliers are not controlled by Ski.com and personal information disclosed to them is subject to the applicable supplier's privacy policy and security practices. Therefore, we encourage you to review the privacy policies of any travel supplier whose products you purchase through this site.
Third-party vendors who provide services or functions on our behalf, including credit card processing, business analytics, customer service, marketing, distribution of surveys or sweepstakes programs, and fraud prevention. We may also authorize third-party vendors to collect information on our behalf, including as necessary to operate features of our website or to facilitate the delivery of online advertising tailored to your interests. Third-party vendors have access to and may collect information only as needed to perform their functions and are not permitted to share or use the information for any other purpose. They are also required to follow the same data security practices that we ourselves adhere to. The information we provide to third parties who provide us with services or act on our behalf is protected by confidentiality agreements and is to be used solely for the purpose(s) permitted by such agreements.
Business partners with whom we may jointly offer products or services, or whose products or services may be offered on our website. You can tell when a third party is involved in a product or service you have requested because their name will appear, either alone or with ours. If you choose to access these optional services, we may share information about you, including your personal information, with those partners. Please note that we do not control the privacy practices of these third-party business partners.
Referring websites
If you were referred to this website from another site (for example, through a link you clicked on another site that directed you to this one), we may share some information about you with that referring website. We have not placed limitations on the referring websites use of your personal information and we encourage you to review the privacy policies of any website that referred you here.
Companies within our corporate family
We may share your personal information with our parent company, S&L Travel Partners, Inc. This sharing enables us to provide you with information about products and services, both travel-related and other, which might interest you. To the extent that our parent company has access to your information, it will follow practices that are at least as restrictive as the practices described in this Privacy Policy. It also will comply with applicable laws governing the transmission of promotional communications and, at a minimum, give you an opportunity in any commercial email they send to choose not to receive such email messages in the future.
We also may share your information:
In response to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process; to establish or exercise our legal rights; to defend against legal claims; or as otherwise required by law. In such cases we reserve the right to raise or waive any legal objection or right available to us.
When we believe it is appropriate to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal or suspected illegal activities; to protect and defend the rights, property, or safety of our company or the Ski.com Services, our customers, or others; and in connection with our Terms of Service and other agreements.In connection with a corporate transaction, such as a divestiture, merger, consolidation, or asset sale, or in the unlikely event of bankruptcy.
Other than as set out above, you will be notified when personal information about you will be shared with third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to have us share such information.
We also may share aggregate or anonymous information with third parties, including suppliers, advertisers, affiliates, investors, and other current and potential business partners. For example, we may tell our advertisers the number of visitors our website receives or the most popular hotels and vacation destinations. This information does not contain any personal information and is used to develop content and services we hope you will find of interest.
Your choices with respect to collection and use of your information
As discussed above, you can choose not to provide us with any information, although it may be needed to book travel or to take advantage of certain features offered on this site.
You also can add or update information and close your account as described above.
You will be given the opportunity to unsubscribe from commercial emails in any such message that we send you. Please note that we reserve the right to send you other communications, including service announcements, administrative messages, and surveys relating either to your account or to your transactions on this site, in some cases without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them.
You may have the opportunity on our website to provide a mobile number in order to receive day-of-travel flight alerts. You may discontinue these alerts at any time.
The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. Please note that if you refuse to accept cookies from this site, you will not be able to access portions of our site.
Cookies and other technologies
Cookies are small data text files and can be stored on your computer's hard drive (if your Web browser permits). This website uses cookies for the following general purposes:
To help us recognize your browser as a previous visitor and save and remember any preferences that may have been set while your browser was visiting our site. For example, if you register on our site, we may use cookies to remember your registration information, so you do not need to log into our site each time you visit. We also may record your password in a cookie, if you checked the box entitled "Keep me signed in." Please note that member IDs, passwords, and any other account-related data included in such cookies are encrypted for security purposes. Unless you register with us, these cookies will not contain any personal information.
To help us customize the content and advertisements provided to you on the website and on other sites across the Internet. For example, when you access a page on our website, a cookie is automatically set by us, our service providers, or our partners to recognize your browser as you navigate on the Internet and to present you with information and advertising based on your apparent interests. See “Display of Advertising/Your Choices” for more information about our online advertising practices and your choices.
To help measure and research the effectiveness of features and offerings of the Service, advertisements, and email communications (by determining which emails you open and act upon).
Most web browsers automatically accept cookies. The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. Please note that if you refuse to accept cookies, you may not be able to access many of the travel tools offered on our sites.
In addition to the above cookies, we use Local Shared Objects, also referred to as "flash cookies," on our web site. These are used to enhance your user experience, for example, by storing your user preferences and settings, such as your volume/mute settings, and in connection with animated content on our website. Local Shared Objects are similar to browser cookies, but can store data more complex than simple text. By themselves, they cannot do anything to or with the data on your computer. Like other cookies, they can only access personally identifiable information that you have provided on this site, and cannot be accessed by other websites. To find out more about flash cookies or how to disable them, please visit: Flash Player help page.
This site may also use Web beacons (also known as clear gifs, pixel tags or Web bugs), which are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, which are placed in the code of a Web page. We use Web beacons to monitor the traffic patterns of users from one page within our sites to another, to deliver or communicate with cookies, to understand whether you have come to our site from an online advertisement displayed on a third-party website, and to improve site performance. We also may allow our service providers to use Web beacons to help us understand which emails have been opened by recipients and to track the visitor traffic and actions on our site. This helps us measure the effectiveness of our content and other offerings.
If you have any questions about our use of cookies or other technologies, please email us at the email below.
Display of tailored advertising/Your choices
Data collected by this website to serve you with relevant advertising Ski.com is committed to providing you with relevant content and information. To do this, we may, through cookies and other technologies, collect information about your travel-related searches on our sites, such as whether you are looking for airline flights or hotels. We use this information, together with other information we have collected about you, to serve you with ads, through our Ski.com Service or elsewhere online, that match your apparent interests.
Please note that we do not combine the information we collect about your travel-related searches on this website with personal information (such as email address) to serve you with ads across other websites. We do not share your personal information with third parties so they can serve you with advertisements. Further, we do not allow third parties to serve ads on our website pages.
Please note that we do not have access to or control over cookies or other technologies third parties may use to collect information about your interests, and the information practices of these third parties are not covered by this Privacy Policy. Some of these companies are members of the Network Advertising Initiative, which offers a single location to opt out of ad targeting from member companies.
Data collected by companies that operate cookie-based exchanges to serve you with relevant advertising
Like other companies operating online, Ski.com participates in cookie-based exchanges where anonymous information is collected about your browsing behavior through cookies and other technologies and segmented into different topics of interest (such as travel). These topics of interest are then shared with third parties, including advertisers and ad networks, so they can tailor advertisements to your apparent interests. We do not share personal information (such as your email address) with these companies and we do not permit these companies to collect any such information about you on our site. Please click here to learn more about cookie-based exchanges, including how to access information about the topics of interest associated with cookies on your computer and how to decline participation in these programs.
Do-Not-Track Signals and Similar Mechanisms
Some web browsers may transmit "do-not-track" signals to websites with which the browser communicates. Because of differences in how web browsers incorporate and activate this feature, it is not always clear whether users intend for these signals to be transmitted, or whether they even are aware of them. Participants in the leading Internet standards-setting organization that is addressing this issue are in the process of determining what, if anything, websites should do when they receive such signals. Ski.com currently does not take action in response to these signals. If and when a final standard is established and accepted, we will reassess how to respond to these signals.
Using the Ski.com Mobile Apps
When you use a Ski.com mobile app, we collect and use information about you in the same way and for the same purposes as we do when you use our website.In addition to this, we also use some other information that we collect automatically when you use our mobile app. Specifically:
We collect information about mobile app functionality that you access and use. This allows us to identify those areas of the mobile app that are of interest to our customers so that we can refine and continuously improve the mobile app. The information we collect for this purpose does not enable us to directly identify you.Each mobile app also sends us the device's unique device identifier (or "UID"), a sequence of numbers or characters that are unique to your mobile device. We use this only on the first opening of the mobile app so that we can confirm to our advertising networks the number of downloads resulting from clicks on their respective ad banners and other marketing tools.
When you use a mobile app, you can choose to allow access to your current location – provided by your mobile device using GPS or similar technologies – in order to identify nearby hotels or airports. If you choose to allow access, this location data may be collected anonymously as part of search requests logged by our servers. We may use your location information to process and personalize your requests, such as by pre-filling the city name when you are searching for travel options (such as a nearby hotel or other travel related service). We may also use location information for internal support, to develop new features, to provide a better user experience, and to improve the overall quality of the Ski.com Service. You can switch off the mobile app’s access to your location at any time through your phone settings menu.
Each mobile app will also send us error-reporting information in the event that it crashes or hangs. This enables us to investigate the error and to improve the stability of the mobile app for future releases. As part of these error reports, the mobile app sends us information about the mobile device type and version, the UID, the time the error occurred, the feature being used and the state of the application when the error occurred. We do not use this information for any purpose other than investigating and remedying the error.
You always have the ability to control what information a mobile app sends to us. You can exercise this control either by changing the settings of the mobile app under its setting menu or changing the settings of your mobile device. Alternatively, you can remove the mobile app from your mobile device entirely and access our services through our website.
How we protect your information
We want you to feel confident about using this website to make travel arrangements, and we are committed to protecting the information we collect. While no website can guarantee security, we have implemented appropriate administrative, technical, and physical security procedures to help protect the personal information you provide to us. For example, only authorized employees are permitted to access personal information, and they may only do so for permitted business functions. In addition, we use encryption when transmitting your sensitive personal information between your system and ours, and we employ firewalls and intrusion detection systems to help prevent unauthorized persons from gaining access to your information.
Children's privacy
This is a general audience website and does not offer services directed to children. Should a child whom we know to be under 13 send personal information to us, we will use that information only to respond directly to that child to inform him or her that we must have parental consent before receiving his or her personal information.
External Links
If any part of this website links you to other sites, those sites do not operate under this Privacy Policy. We recommend you examine the privacy statements posted on those other websites to understand their procedures for collecting, using, and disclosing personal information.
Visiting our website from outside the United States
If you are visiting our website from outside the United States, please be aware that your information may be transferred to, stored, and processed in the United States, where our servers are located and our central database is operated. The data protection and other laws of the United States and other countries might not be as comprehensive as those in your country, but please be assured that we take steps to ensure that your privacy is protected. By using our services, you understand that your information may be transferred to our facilities and those third parties with whom we share it as described in this Policy.
Agreement to Ski.com Terms of Use
Your use of the Service is also subject to Ski.com’s Terms of Use. Any disputes related to this Privacy Policy shall be governed by the dispute resolution provisions of the Terms of Use (including but not limited to its provisions concerning arbitration), which are incorporated here by reference.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
We may update this Privacy Policy in the future. We will notify you about material changes to this Privacy Policy by sending a notice to the email address you provided to us or by placing a prominent notice on our website.
How you can contact us
If you have questions about either this Privacy Policy (or your travel planning or purchases), please Contact Us or write to us at the following address:
Ski.comAABC 210, Suite AAAspen, CO 81611Attn: Privacy TeamThis Privacy Policy is effective as of May 21, 2018.**
What we doLodgingLift TicketsEquipment RentalsFlightsTransfersRental CarsLessonsActivitiesTravel InsurancePARTNERSHIPS & SERVICESAffiliatesMeeting & Event TraxTravel Agent LoginPartner LoginGroupsPLAN YOUR SKI VACATIONSki ResortsSki Resort AccommodationsSki Vacation Package DealsSki Vacation Travel InsuranceBook Online20-21 Ski Vacation GuideFirst Ski TripHeli/CatTo The Mountains TripsCOMPANY INFORMATIONMountain Travel ExpertsAbout UsFrequently Asked QuestionsContact UsTerms & ConditionsPrivacy StatementPress RoomJobsCustomer ReviewsTo The MountainsPopular SearchesJapan Ski TripsSki In Ski Out LodgingFamily Ski TripsAll Inclusive Ski PackagesPowder SkiingCheap Ski VacationsEpic Pass vs. Ikon PassWhere Is It Snowing?Ski GlossarySki.comFacebookTwitterYouTubeSki.com BlogInstagram2020SKI.COM All rights reserved.NewsletterSIGN UP HERE to get the latest deals, news and snow reports at top resorts worldwide.Call1-800-908-5000Quoterequest a free quote×To The Mountains Newsletter Sign up for the To The Mountains Newsletter to receive expert-curated deals, trip guides and snow news.Email: *First Name: *Last Name: *I have an Epic PassI have an Ikon PassSubmitClose
